I've had the trail on my bucket list
for about 10 years.
...and wanting to do it, because
I understand there's a lot of—
a lot of emotion that goes into
a 100-kilometer hike over five days,
and a lot of sense of being...
in bonding with people that are
40 years younger than you,
and seeing people from all over the world.
Having somebody Sherpa your belongings
from town to town,
so you can really focus on the hike.
The only way to go.
Makes it a really great trip in a lot of ways,
because for one, I'm not carrying it all on my back.
And two, there's nothing better than laying down
in a nice clean bed and a shower
after a long day of hiking.
I won't be sleeping in a tent or at some hostel,
so I'm glad we're doing it this way.
We started our planning about eight months ago.
We have been very happy with
the level of communication,
the level of efforts, the way
they've kind of packaged together,
informed us about the package,
told us what to prepare
to get over here, making it
an outstanding experience.
Effortless outside of the hike.
Accommodation was great, was excellent.
Our bags arrived in the hotels.
I would definitely recommend Santiago Ways.
They were incredibly helpful and
fantastic organising our trip.
It is special because of
the feelings it gives you,
the magic that is around it,
and the people that you meet.
Buen Camino!